[{"answer": "It's -- you know, it's difficult to say until you actually make the show.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "What makes this different to \"Idol\"?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "You can be 12.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Why is this a different show?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well, you're quite.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Is that going to be a key weapon do you think in your ratings and so on \"X Factor America\"?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, look, where they start is where you want them to end up.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "So you can see who are the real performers, right?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "OWELL: Because I made, you know, a lot of money.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Why did you take this huge gamble?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "When did you get bored being -- what was a highly paid performing monkey in the end?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, you don't have any control.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Can we?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "You're a monkey.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "It has to be a gamble.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "It's a gamble, isn't it?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Always.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Has any part of you contemplated the unthinkable?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Well, thank you.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Would you accept that?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I got really emotional, I mean genuinely.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "What was it like for you that moment, honestly, when you realized that was it, you were walking away from the show that had made you a global superstar?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "I kind of welled up a bit, yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Any tears that night?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Certainly.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Did you think it was a mistake to get rid of Paula?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "ORGAN: What do you think of Steven Tyler and J. Lo?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Hilarious.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Does that make you laugh?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I can't imagine it.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, I can tell you now.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Is it fame, power, or money?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Should we go back to the fame and power?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Yes, but you wouldn't do it for nothing, would you?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Yes, for sure.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "They were really -- you know, honest to god, they were just cool about it.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "What advice did your parents give you then?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "When my dad died was the worst time in my life, as you know.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "If that wasn't the worst time in your life, what was?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "It's really like Colin Firth and the (INAUDIBLE) and the fountain in \"Bridget Jones.\"", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "What's the problem?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Fighting, you know?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I can't lie.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "What was that day like for you when you look back on it?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Best advice.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What was the best advice he gave you?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "We fight.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "She is probably the only woman I know who actually has any kind of control over you, isn't she?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Honestly, I can't remember, Piers, but I'm now 12 years old, I'm not going to say sorry.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "What was it about?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Well, not exactly, no.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "You're quite a mommy's boy, aren't you?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Well, she comes up to me.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "When you're in England, you have Sunday lunch with her almost every Sunday, don't you?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "I hope not.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Is it going to happen to us?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "I was -- I was talking to a friend of mine last year where we had this conversation where everything got a bit bleak last year.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Is it the -- is the intense attention now from the Internet, from TMZ, from -- has the game changed for celebrities?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Yes, he offered me I think it was 150,000 grand to criticize him bonking his wife.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Didn't you get offered some huge six figure sum by a guy in a restaurant in L.A. once?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Because -- no.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Why wouldn't you do that?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "And was it going to be that night.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "If you're watching, I'll even do it for 50,000 dollars, OK?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "-- the boudoir.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "The what?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "A sex god -- boudoir.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Do you think you're a bit of a sex god?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Let's take the boy out of the tabloids.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "What is happening to you?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I just wondered do you look in the mirror sometimes and think, \"Whoa\"--", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "A sex god?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Hmm.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "No seriously?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "I like it.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Do you care that it's shallow?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "I'm on CNN now.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Where are you getting your language from today?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I haven't been invited.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Are you going to the royal wedding?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "I don't know William.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "What do you think of William and Kate?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Yes, well you think -- I -- I can remember those awful shots as the two of them, you know, on -- on -- on the funeral.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "I can't believe in America they're going crazy for it, aren't they?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Are you a monarchist?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "I -- I -- I do -- certainly for our own country I do, because I think it -- it's just something which -- which makes us unique.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "Do you believe in the institution of monarchy, unelected?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "I mean, do you sing?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Not well.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "Do you dance?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "Badly.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Do you do impressions?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Can you act?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "Can you do trapeze acts?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Managed that a few times.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Juggling?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "At times.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Fire eating?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "-- what would you declare as your talent, if you had to?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "I'm good at spotting somebody else's talent.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "ORGAN: Or paying of death, what would you say you -- was your talent?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "That's it.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Apart from that, what is the -- what is the tangible talent?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "Oh, no.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Yes, but if you had to?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "High diving.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "If you had to produce your own talent, do you have a secret one we don't know about?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "He's this high.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "He's cool, right?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "I think he's -- I think he's really talented, really musical.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "What do you make of him?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "I am 47.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "And how old are you, Susan?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "I'm going to sing \"I Dreamed A Dream\" from \"Les Miserables.\"", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "What are you going to sing tonight?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "And we both thought this was a preposterous moment where this little old lady from -- or middle aged lady from Scotland was just going to come on and be a complete train wreck, didn't we?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "Wasn't it amazing?", "qSentId": 743}, {"answer": "Elton John gave you a bit of a whack the other day.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "I mean, how can that be a bad thing?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "He said -- similar kind of thing.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "What did he say?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "We're going to come back after another short break.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "Why do they say bad things about me?", "qSentId": 791}, {"answer": "Go on.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 806, "question": "But I've gone a little bit further this time, Piers?", "qSentId": 805}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 809, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 808}, {"answer": "Five million.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 811, "question": "Five million?", "qSentId": 810}, {"answer": "No, I know.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "That's your show as well?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "I don't think that shows in general have produced enough global stars, if I'm being honest with you.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 833, "question": "Do you think you're going to get the same kind of success in America?", "qSentId": 832}, {"answer": "We're looking.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 838, "question": "And what about a host?", "qSentId": 837}, {"answer": "Yes, Piers.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 840, "question": "I was wondering if you've chosen one yet?", "qSentId": 839}, {"answer": "I've got an idea.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 842, "question": "Have you?", "qSentId": 841}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 854, "question": "So be -- it's going to be two people?", "qSentId": 853}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 856, "question": "Are they American?", "qSentId": 855}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "Two American -- man, woman?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "Well, I think I'm good at it, Piers.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 871, "question": "Have you thought about it?", "qSentId": 870}, {"answer": "Well -- well, we start in Los Angeles at the Sports Arena.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 892, "question": "How can they join in the X-Factor party in America?", "qSentId": 891}, {"answer": "These are without the judges.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 895, "question": "These are without the judges, right?", "qSentId": 894}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 910, "question": "Are you nervous?", "qSentId": 909}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "110405pmt", "aSentId": 916, "question": "Do you really?", "qSentId": 915}]